Hello everyone and welcome to a new video here on my channel!
Die Monique is a brand from Poland and just launched their collection Black Rose
and they sent me a selection of this collection. That sounds funny.
So I'm trying on four different outfits today and I'm going to show them to you and I really think that these looks are super cool for like clubbing and fetish parties and also maybe for daily wear.
I think I'll start with a two-piece set combined of these panties and this top.
I'm really curious about the fabric because it looks cool with the print.
You'll see more of it in a second.
This is the outfit. Some would call it, I don't know, lingerie, others would say it's a climbing outfit.
I combine it with my Fernando Benin boots because the crotch high which looks perfectly together with the panty cut here.
So the shorter the pants the better for the boots. I don't know.
But I think it is really a great outfit.
And I also like that view of this outfit.
and I also like the fabric so this rose pattern here on this material is like a thick wet look
really soft and yeah I think it's something different apart from all the plain normal
color fabrics so to say this is a great outfit for clothing in summer for example
when the nights are really warm and I do have to say the boots are keeping you warm as well
or maybe just for like special occasions at home who knows it's up to you if you
like to top but you think that the panties are too much or low-cut or over
the top haha then there's another option an alternative because there are some
jeans in this fabric which apparently go pretty well together with a top and I'm
I'm going to show them to you now.
So this is the combination with the long pants.
Of course I had to change my shoes.
Wearing some Giaros now and no boots.
And I have to say, I like this combination as well.
Although I think I prefer the short panty somehow,
which is kind of weird for me.
But anyway, it is really comfortable.
So it's also stretchy.
I'm wearing size small. I think everything I have here is size small and it's also the smallest size.
And I also really do like that the pants have pockets on the back side which is not usual or not common, whatever.
I think this is like for colder days or just to stroll in the city maybe.
It's up to you.
If you do not like the pattern or think that it is too much, there are also other fabrics
in this collection.
For example this one shoulder dress with a plain wet look fabric and I'm going to try
this one next.
It's a rather plain dress and it's a bit too wide in my waist here so I added a belt.
So it is a great basic outfit to pile accessories on top of it and to make
really good look with it. Yeah I just added a belt and bracelet and my Swedish
collar so this is just an inspiration to pimp up basics in general. I like this
dress very much, it's so comfortable and I'm really a fan of this one shoulder cut.
So I like it as it is and the fabric is not too thick so it's also good for
summer for example. I'm really happy with the overall look. The last outfit is
going to be a two-piece set again and a faux leather look. So again a different material
and another combination top and skirt. Let's do it. This is the last outfit. As I said
it is kind of a faux leather and I changed up a bit. As you can see on the product picture
The skirt is really high up here, but I pulled it down and I turned the waistband here down.
So it's a different look, but I think I like this one better.
I really like the top.
It is rather plain, but it is cool basic.
I'm sure I'll combine it with lots of different outfits because it is just something you can
use for every occasion.
As for the skirt, I think I need to pick it up.
Yeah, anyway, in total I really like the outfit, I really like the length of the skirt and
the material feels really nice as well.
DeMonique is a rather young brand founded in 2012.
As I said they are from Poland and you can find the pieces at selected shops or simply
online.
I'll link the homepage of course down below the video.
So if you kinda counted the outfits and the boxes you may have noticed that there is one
additional box standing here I didn't show yet.
This is a catsuit from a different collection.
So everything I showed you so far was Black Rose 2.
This is the Silver Thread collection and I decided to do a special jumpsuit up video
with this one you'll see in a few weeks here on my channel.
I hope you enjoyed this video, I hope you like this brand and I could show you some
new outfit or inspirations.
Have a nice day, leave a comment down below the video, check out everything I link in
the description box and see you around, bye!